<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<UbariProjects
	xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
	<Project>
		<h1>Construction of National Legal Training Centre</h1>
		<h3>Overview</h3>
		<p>Candy carrot cake gummies gummi bears jujubes cupcake. Tiramisu chocolate candy canes cookie muffin pudding pastry. Jelly-o bonbon ice cream tart cotton candy apple pie ice cream gummi bears sweet roll.</p>
		<img>https://cdn.pixabay.com/photo/2018/07/15/10/44/dna-3539309__340.jpg</img>
	</Project>
	<Project>
		<h1>Rehabilitation of Al Gurdhabia School - External Works</h1>
		<h3>Overview</h3>
		<p>Oat cake donut lollipop marzipan shortbread. Drage pudding cake muffin cheesecake cupcake cookie. Candy canes cupcake bear claw sweet roll sesame snaps jelly. Apple pie pudding danish cake halvah gummi bears cotton candy muffin.</p>
		<img>https://cdn.pixabay.com/photo/2015/05/28/14/53/ux-788002__340.jpg</img>
	</Project>
	<Project>
		<h1>Rehabilitation of Aquba Ben Nafaa School</h1>
		<h3>Overview</h3>
		<p>Bonbon lemon drops caramels donut pudding. Icing dragee tiramisu jujubes cotton candy jelly-o caramels caramels icing. Dragee donut pudding liquorice gingerbread chocolate cake lollipop. Shortbread macaroon ice cream biscuit cake jelly-o lemon drops croissant.</p>
		<img>https://cdn.pixabay.com/photo/2016/11/19/14/00/code-1839406__340.jpg</img>
	</Project>
	<Project>
		<h1>Rehabilitation of Disa School</h1>
		<h3>Overview</h3>
		<p>Topping candy canes cupcake sweet roll liquorice gingerbread. Biscuit shortbread carrot cake tootsie roll sugar plum liquorice bonbon. Oat cake shortbread tiramisu dragee bear claw cotton candy jelly.</p>
		<img>https://cdn.pixabay.com/photo/2015/12/04/14/05/code-1076536__340.jpg</img>
	</Project>
	<Project>
		<h1>Rehabilitation of Gil Saade School</h1>
		<h3>Overview</h3>
		<p>Jelly tiramisu marshmallow ice cream powder icing. Gingerbread topping liquorice macaroon dragee icing gummies jujubes shortbread. Bonbon bonbon donut sesame snaps tart lollipop gingerbread. Pastry tootsie roll sweet chupa chups gummi bears shortbread danish marshmallow.</p>
		<img>https://cdn.pixabay.com/photo/2017/08/01/22/38/flash-2568381__340.jpg</img>
	</Project>
	<Project>
		<h1>Rehabilitation of Obari Civil Airports taxiway and aircraft standing area</h1>
		<h3>Overview</h3>
		<p>Dessert chocolate wafer shortbread oat cake. Brownie cake chupa chups danish chocolate cake jelly chocolate cake candy. Chocolate biscuit gummi bears croissant lemon drops icing lemon drops apple pie chocolate cake.</p>
		<img>https://cdn.pixabay.com/photo/2015/01/09/11/11/office-594132__340.jpg</img>
	</Project>
	<Project>
		<h1>Rehabilitation of Obari Main Entrance Roundabout</h1>
		<h3>Overview</h3>
		<p>Souffle cupcake topping lollipop cupcake lemon drops sweet roll cheesecake macaroon. Dragee cookie candy canes chocolate bar brownie. Jelly-o brownie cotton candy gingerbread gummies. Muffin lemon drops macaroon sesame snaps candy ice cream.</p>
		<img>https://cdn.pixabay.com/photo/2018/05/18/15/30/web-design-3411373__340.jpg</img>
	</Project>
	<Project>
		<h1>Rehabilitation of Soccer Fields at Gil Saade and Al-Disa Primary Schools</h1>
		<h3>Overview</h3>
		<p>Dragee biscuit bear claw marzipan gummi bears. Topping donut dragee pastry icing pudding. Pastry souffle bonbon pie jujubes biscuit cheesecake sugar plum cheesecake.</p>
		<img>https://cdn.pixabay.com/photo/2014/11/24/16/35/embryo-544192__340.jpg</img>
	</Project>
	<Project>
		<h1>Rehabilitation of Ubari Primary School</h1>
		<h3>Overview</h3>
		<p>Tootsie roll sugar plum candy canes bonbon muffin gingerbread. Gingerbread dessert jelly marshmallow powder bonbon jelly donut. Croissant icing souffle tart marzipan cake sweet. Wafer powder danish jelly-o biscuit lemon drops fruitcake macaroon marshmallow.</p>
		<img>https://cdn.pixabay.com/photo/2016/04/20/08/21/entrepreneur-1340649__340.jpg</img>
	</Project>
	<Project>
		<h1>Rehabilitation of Ubari University of Arts and Science</h1>
		<h3>Overview</h3>
		<p>Caramels jelly-o cookie sesame snaps gummies sugar plum. Tiramisu toffee sugar plum chocolate cake chupa chups sesame snaps pudding. Apple pie dragee macaroon sugar plum dessert.</p>
		<img>https://cdn.pixabay.com/photo/2015/12/07/10/58/architect-1080592__340.jpg</img>
	</Project>
</UbariProjects>